A Guide to the Virginia War History Commission, 1915-1931
Library of Virginia
- Series VI: County Source Material, 1919-1927
  - Goochland County
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Hobson, Bland (Vol. III, p. 28) (Box 54, Folder 34)
      - Hobson, R.C. (Vol. III, p. 28) (Box 54, Folder 35)
      - Lawrence, George M. (Vol. III, p. 33) (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Grayson County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Grayson County in War Time by F.H. Wilson (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - Virginia Schools and Colleges (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 54, Folder 40)
    - Red Cross in Virginia (Box 54, Folder 41)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 54, Folder 42)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Editorial - Grayson Gazette, 13 April 1918 (Box 54, Folder 43)
      - Brewer, C. Keith (Vol. III, p. 8) (Box 54, Folder 44)
      - Combs, Walter H. (Vol. III, p. 15) (Box 54, Folder 45)
      - Hampton, Gene (Vol. III, p. 25) (Box 54, Folder 46)
      - James, W.H. (Vol. III, p. 30) (Box 54, Folder 47)
      - McGee, Marion (Vol. III, p. 35) (Box 54, Folder 48)
      - Poe, Carlisle (Vol. III, p. 43) (Box 54, Folder 49)
      - Vaughan, L.M. (Vol. III, p. 60) (Box 54, Folder 50)
      - Williams, Ralph E. (Vol. III, p. 63) (Box 54, Folder 51)
      - Unidentified (Box 54, Folder 52)
    - Post-War Conditions and Activities (Box 54, Folder 53)
  - Greene County
    - Virginia Schools and Colleges (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Greensville County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Greensville County in War Time by W.B. Goodwyn (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Virginians of Distinguished Service - Colonel E.E. Goodry (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Draft Law and Virginia Organizations (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Beman, C.E. (Vol. III, p. 6) (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Short, William E. (Vol. III, p. 52 & one letter omitted) (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous - copy of Independent Messenger (9 March 1923) -See Oversize Box 4 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Halifax County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Halifax County in War Time by Samuel Lee Adams (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Hanover County
    - Pre-War Conditions and Activities (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Henry County
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Pannill, George Edward & Pannill, Jeb Stuart (Vol. III, p. 41) (Box 55, Folder 18)
      - reamey, George (Vol. III, p. 45) (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Highland County
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Red Cross in Virginia (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Post-War Conditions and Activities (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Isle of Wight County
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - James City County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - James City County and Williamsburg in War Time by Mabel Bradford Friend (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Red Cross in Virginia (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Jennings, Nathaniel Hall (Vol. III, p. 30) (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - King and Queen County
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - King William County
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - Draft Law and Virginia Organizations - Records of Soldiers and Sailors (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Lancaster County
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Draft Law and Virginia Organizations (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - Red Cross in Virginia (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Loudoun County
    - Pre-War Conditions and Activities (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 55, Folder 34)
    - Draft Law and Virginia Organizations
      - War Record of William C. Ferguson (Box 55, Folder 35)
      - War Record of Richard Fishburn (Box 55, Folder 36)
      - War Record of Arthur Hawling Fulton (Box 55, Folder 37)
      - War Record of Alfred Glascock (Box 55, Folder 38)
      - War Record of Conrad Harrison Goodwin (Box 55, Folder 39)
      - War Record of Robert Goodwin (Box 55, Folder 40)
      - War Record of William Pinkeny Herbert (Box 55, Folder 41)
      - War Record of William H. Jenkins (Box 55, Folder 42)
      - War Record of Charles Carter Riticor (Box 55, Folder 43)
      - War Record of Robert A. Riticor (Box 55, Folder 44)
      - War Record of Armstead Rust (Box 55, Folder 45)
      - War Record of Benjamin Heath White (Box 55, Folder 46)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 55, Folder 47)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Adams, Harry - Incident on "President Lincoln" (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Goodwin, Conrad H. (Vol. III, p. 23) (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Rust, Armistead (Vol. III, p. 50) (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Singleton, Anne (Vol. III, p. 53) (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Varne, F.B. (Vol. III, p. 60) (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Photogrphs of 305th Engineers (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Post-War Activities and Conditions (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Louisa County
    - Pre-War Conditions and Activities (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Schools and Colleges (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Hood, Curtis R. (Vol. III, p. 28) (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - "Joe" (Vol. III, p. 30) (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - Willis, Wyndham R. (Vol. III, p. 63) (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Lunenburg County
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Neblett, H.C. (Vol. III, p. 39) (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - Walker, T.R. (omitted from Volume III) (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Madison County
    - Virginians of Distinguished Service - Local Civilians Roll of Honor (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Schools and Colleges (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Post-War Conditions and Activities (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Mathews County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Mathews County in War Time by Bertha Foster (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Post-War Conditions and Activities (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Mecklenburg County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Mecklenburg County in War Time by F.C. Bedinger (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Virginians of Distinguished Service - Earle Davis Gregory (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Draft Law and Virginia Organizations (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Wilmoth, E.M. (Vol. III, p. 63) (Box 56, Folder 31)
      - Roberts, Frank (Vol. III, p. 47) (Box 56, Folder 31)
      - Allen, Claude W. (Vol. III, p. 1) (Box 56, Folder 31)
      - Touery, George R. (Vol. III, p. 58) (Box 56, Folder 31)
      - Anderson, R.L. (Vol. III, p. 2) (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Montgomery County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Montgomery County in War Time by Charles W. Crush (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Nansemond County
    - Draft Law and Virginia Organizations (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Nelson County
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - New Kent County
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Norfolk County
    - Draft Law and Military Organizations - List of Dead (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 56, Folder 38)
    - Red Cross in Virginia (Box 56, Folder 39)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 56, Folder 40)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Jaffe, Louis I. (Vol. III, p. 29) (Box 56, Folder 41)
      - Moss, James (Vol. III, p. 39) (Box 56, Folder 42)
      - Page, Frank (Vol. III, p. 41) (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - Northampton County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Northampton County Community History by F.F. Buchanan (Box 56, Folder 44)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 56, Folder 45)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 56, Folder 46)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 56, Folder 47)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Doughty, E.J., Jr. (Vol. III, p. 18) (Box 56, Folder 48)
  - Northumberland County
    - Red Cross in Virginia (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Post-War Conditions and Activities (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Nottoway County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Nottoway County in War Time by Agnes Epes (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Draft Law and Virginia Organizations - The Final Roster, edited by Walter Cobb (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Orange County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Orange County in War Time by Sarah Bennett Carter (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Pre-War Conditions and Activities (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Draft Law and Virginia Organizations (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Page County
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Patrick County
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Pittsylvania County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Pittsylvania County in the World War by Mrs. N.E. Clement (See Also Oversize) (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Powhatan County
    - Pre-War Conditions and Activities (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Prince Edward County
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - With "Old Eph" in the Army (Not a History): A Simple Treatise on the Human Side of the Colored Soldier by Walker H. Jordan (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Post-War Conditions and Activities (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Prince George County
    - History of Prince George County taken from Howe's Collection of Virginia (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Wood, Jordan (Vol. III, p. 64) (Box 57, Folder 26)
      - Miscellaneous Newspaper Articles (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Prince William County
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Virginia Schools and Colleges (Box 57, Folder 29)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Princess Anne County
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 57, Folder 31)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 57, Folder 32)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Washburn, Paul deB (Vol. III, p. 61) (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Rappahannock County
    - Pre-War Conditions and Activities (Box 57, Folder 34)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 57, Folder 35)
    - Virginia Schools and Colleges (Box 57, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous Letters and Incidents (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - Richmond County
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - Roanoke County
    - Pre-War Conditions and Activities (Box 57, Folder 39)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 57, Folder 40)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 57, Folder 41)
    - Post-War Conditions and Activities (Box 57, Folder 42)
  - Rockbridge County
    - Editorials from Rockbridge County News (Box 57, Folder 43)
    - Virginia Schools and Colleges (Box 57, Folder 44)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 57, Folder 45)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Roadcap, Robert Swinton (Vol. III, p. 47) (Box 57, Folder 46)
      - Ruff, Millo L. (Vol. III, p. 50) (Box 57, Folder 47)
      - Wilson, T.P. (Vol. III, p. 63) (Box 57, Folder 48)
  - Rockingham County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Rockingham County and the City of Harrisonburg in the World War (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Pre-War Conditions and Activities (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Schools and Colleges (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - "Rockingham County's Contribution to the World War," by Genoa Swecker (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Coffman, Frank (Vol. III, p. 14) (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - War Record of John Heller Crawn (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Ruebush, William H. (Vol. III, p. 49-50) (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Russell County
    - Pre-War Conditions and Activities (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Schools and Colleges (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Scott County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Scott County History by Robert Milford Addington (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Shenandoah County
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Schools and Colleges (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Copy of General Order 19 (Box 58, Folder 17)
      - Aiken, Charles L. (Vol. III, p. 1) (Box 58, Folder 18)
      - Allen, William (Vol. III, p. 1) (Box 58, Folder 19)
      - Anonymous (Vol. III, p. 3) (Box 58, Folder 20)
      - Baker, William (Vol. III, p. 5) (Box 58, Folder 21)
      - Bean, Charles E. (Vol. III, p. 5) (Box 58, Folder 22)
      - Blanchfield, C.A. (Vol. III, p. 7) (Box 58, Folder 23)
      - Borum, Charles J. (Vol. III, p. 7) (Box 58, Folder 24)
      - Brill, Guy C. (Vol. III, p. 8) (Box 58, Folder 25)
      - Burchfield, J.C. (Vol. III, p. 9) (Box 58, Folder 26)
      - Burke, Edgar W. (Vol. III, p. 9) (Box 58, Folder 27)
      - Campbell, Forest J. (Vol. III, p. 10) (Box 58, Folder 28)
      - Campbell, Joseph C. (Vol. III, p. 10) (Box 58, Folder 29)
      - "Carl" (Box 58, Folder 30)
      - Clinedinst, Walter (Vol. III, p. 12) (Box 58, Folder 31)
      - Cloughety, C.R. (Vol. III, p. 12) (Box 58, Folder 32)
      - Coffman, J.F. (Vol. III, p. 14) (Box 58, Folder 33)
      - Conrad, Stanley Ramon (Vol. III, p. 15) (Box 58, Folder 34)
      - Davison, R.B. (Vol. III, p. 17) (Box 58, Folder 35)
      - Dellinger, Aden M. (Vol. III p. 17) (Box 58, Folder 36)
      - Dellinger, Perry G. (Vol. III, p. 17) (Box 58, Folder 37)
      - Dever, Frank (Vol. III, p. 17) (Box 58, Folder 38)
      - Dirting, John Landon (Vol. III, p. 18) (Box 58, Folder 39)
      - Drummonds, Ashby (Vol. III, p. 18) (Box 58, Folder 40)
      - Fisher, Robert C. (Vol. III, p. 20) (Box 58, Folder 41)
      - "Fred" (Vol. III, p. 21) (Box 58, Folder 42)
      - French, Warren (Vol. III, p. 21) (Box 58, Folder 43)
      - Getz, Russell B. (Vol. III, p. 22) (Box 58, Folder 44)
      - Godlove, Ernest W. (Vol. III, p. 22) (Box 58, Folder 45)
      - Good, Lee J. (Vol. III, p. 22) (Box 58, Folder 46)
      - Goode, S.S. (Vol. III, p. 22) (Box 58, Folder 47)
      - Gordon, Gorman G. (Vol. III, p. 23) (Box 58, Folder 48)
      - Guard, Ben (Vol. III, p. 24) (Box 58, Folder 49)
      - Guard, Henry (Vol. III, p. 24) (Box 58, Folder 50)
      - Hammon, C.F. (Vol. III, p. 25) (Box 58, Folder 51)
      - Hepner, William S. (Vol. III, p. 27) (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Hesley, Orie L. (Vol. III, p. 27) (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Himebright, A.H. (Vol. III, p. 27) (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Hupp, Russell T. (Vol. III, p. 29) (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - "James" (Vol. III, p. 29) (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - "John" (Vol. III, p. 30) (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Karg, Florence (Vol. III, p. 31) (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Keister, John W. (Vol. III, p. 31) (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Keller, Hugh L. (Vol. III, p. 31) (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Kemp, J.J. (Vol. III, p. 31) (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Kronk, Jesse W. (Vol. III, p. 33) (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Lake, Arthur J. (Vol. III, p. 33) (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - Link, Gilbert (Vol. III, p. 34) (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - Link, Raymond W. (Vol. III, p. 34) (Box 59, Folder 14)
      - Long, Bruce M. (Vol. III, p. 34) (Box 59, Folder 15)
      - Long, Turner A. (Vol. III, p. 34) (Box 59, Folder 16)
      - Lutz, Mrs. N.L. (Vol. III, p. 35) (Box 59, Folder 17)
      - Lytton, Byrd (Vol. III, p. 35) (Box 59, Folder 18)
      - McInturff, C. Stanley (Vol. III, p. 35) (Box 59, Folder 19)
      - McInturff, Dorsey (Vol. III, p. 35) (Box 59, Folder 20)
      - Middleton, Benjamin H. (Vol. III, p. 38) (Box 59, Folder 21)
      - Middleton, G. Wesley (Vol. III, p. 38) (Box 59, Folder 22)
      - Middleton, Isaac (Vol. III, p. 38) (Box 59, Folder 23)
      - Miller, Norman L. (Vol. III, p. 38) (Box 59, Folder 24)
      - Miller, Solomon S. (Vol. III, p. 38) (Box 59, Folder 25)
      - Minave?, Lester (omitted from Volume III) (Box 59, Folder 26)
      - Mitchell, Clarence (Vol. III, p. 38) (Box 59, Folder 27)
      - Newland, Fred (Vol. III, p. 40) (Box 59, Folder 28)
      - Orndorff, Alfred L. (Vol. III, p. 41) (Box 59, Folder 29)
      - Racey, John N. (Vol. III, p. 45) (Box 59, Folder 30)
      - Richard, F.L. (Vol. III, p. 46) (Box 59, Folder 31)
      - Ritenour, Arthur (Vol. III, p. 47) (Box 59, Folder 32)
      - Ritenur, Russell M. (Vol. III, p. 47 & letter omitted from Volume III) (Box 59, Folder 33)
      - Rittenour, Fred A. (Vol. III, p. 47) (Box 59, Folder 34)
      - Rittenour, William F. (Vol. III, p. 47) (Box 59, Folder 35)
      - Rudolph, F.L. (Vol. III, p. 49) (Box 59, Folder 36)
      - Rudolph, Leonard (Vol. III, p. 49) (Box 59, Folder 37)
      - Rudolph, Mahlon (Vol. III, p. 49) (Box 59, Folder 38)
      - Santimer, Orland Bryan (Vol. III, p. 51) (Box 59, Folder 39)
      - Schweinfurt, Henry F. (Vol. III, p. 51) (Box 59, Folder 40)
      - Shaffer, Joe M. (Vol. III, p. 51) (Box 59, Folder 41)
      - Sibert, Tressel (Vol. III, p. 52) (Box 59, Folder 42)
      - Sigler, Elmer K. (Vol. III, p. 52) (Box 59, Folder 43)
      - Smith, John P. (Vol. III, p. 53) (Box 59, Folder 44)
      - Snapp, Elmer J. (Vol. III, p. 54) (Box 59, Folder 45)
      - Snyder, C.L. (Vol. III, p. 54) (Box 59, Folder 46)
      - Stanley, George G. (Vol. III, p. 54) (Box 59, Folder 47)
      - Weatherholtz, Archie E. (Vol. III, p. 62) (Box 59, Folder 48)
      - Zirkle, Harry (Vol. III, p. 65) (Box 59, Folder 49)
      - Zirkle, Matthew Doll (Vol. III, p. 65) (Box 59, Folder 50)
      - University Farm School, Allery, France and "The Plowshare" Farm School Journal (Box 59, Folder 51)
  - Smyth County
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 59, Folder 52)
  - Southampton County
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Barlow, Hunter G. (Vol. III, p. 5) (Box 59, Folder 53)
  - Stafford County
    - Pre-War Conditions and Activities (Box 53, Folder 54)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 59, Folder 55)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 59, Folder 56)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 59, Folder 57)
  - Surry County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Surry County in Time of War by A.W. Bohannan (Box 59, Folder 58)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 59, Folder 59)
    - Draft Law and Virginia Organizations (Box 59, Folder 60)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 59, Folder 61)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 59, Folder 62)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Allen, Eugene S. (Vol. III, p. 1) (Box 59, Folder 63)
      - Barnes, Fred W. (Vol. III, p. 5) (Box 59, Folder 64)
      - Burgess, Shirley B. (omitted from Volume III) (Box 59, Folder 65)
      - Fuqua, J.W. (Vol. III, p. 21) (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Hunnicutt, James C. (Vol. III, p. 29) (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Remoussenard, Alphonsine (Vol. III, p. 46) (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Saunders, Bennie Elliott (Vol. III, p. 51) (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Spratley, Warren (Vol. III, p. 54) (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Post-War Conditions and Activities (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Sussex County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Sussex County in War Time by Gayle Hartz Ellis (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Tazewell County
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Draft Law and Virginia Organizations (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Warren County
    - County Historial Material (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Draft Law and Virginia Organizations (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Warwick County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Warwick County in War Time by Elizabeth Madison (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Washington County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Washington County in War Time by Mrs. Alexander Stuart (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Wise County
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Wise County in War Time by Mrs. R. Tate Irvine (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Wythe County
    - Pre-War Conditions and Activities (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Johnson, Frank McP. (Vol. III, p. 30) (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Unidentified Locality
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 60, Folder 30)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Unidentified (Box 60, Folder 31)
      - Laws, Charles T. (omitted from Volume III) (Box 60, Folder 32)
      - Morton, A.K. (Vol. III, p. 39) (Box 60, Folder 33)
      - Unidentified (Box 60, Folder 34)
      - Unidentified (Box 60, Folder 35)
      - Unidentified Photographs (Box 60, Folder 36)
      - Sketch of Service of Assistant Surgeon W. Armisted Gills (Box 60, Folder 37)
      - List of Officers who served as Naval Attaches from August 1914 to November 1918 with Embassies (Box 60, Folder 38)
      - Information Relative to the Work of the Virginia State Board of Medical Examiners, 1916-1923 (Box 60, Folder 39)
      - "Poems" by Devereux Maitland Myers, 1919 (Box 60, Folder 40)
- City Source Material, 1919-1927